<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Filmoteca_AndreRM</string>

    <!--Pantalla 1-->
    <string name="welcome_title">Welcome to Filmoteca</string>
    <string name="welcome_subtitle">Your multimedia content platform</string>
    <string name="btn_enter">Enter</string>


    <!--Pantalla 2-->
    <string name="login_fondo">Email</string>
    <string name="login_password_hint">Password</string>
    <string name="login_button">Log in</string>
    <string name="login_register_link">Don’t have an account? Register</string>
    <string name="error_email">Incorrect email</string>
    <string name="error_password">Incorrect password</string>
    <string name="error_login">Email or Password Fail</string>

    <!--Registro-->
    <string name="register_username">Username</string>
    <string name="register_email">Email</string>
    <string name="register_telefone">Number Telefone</string>
    <string name="register_passworld">Passworld</string>
    <string name="register_passworld_confirm">Repit Passworld</string>
    <string name="register_title">New User</string>
    <string name="register_button_confirm">Register</string>

    <string name="register_error_empty">All fields are required</string>
    <string name="register_error_passworld">Password confirmation does not match</string>
    <string name="register_error_user_exist">This user account already exists</string>
    <string name="register_ok">Register Okay</string>

    <!--Lista plataformas-->
    <string name="menu_ayuda">Help</string>
    <string name="menu_acerca_de">About us</string>
    <string name="menu_title_bar">Streamify</string>
    <string name="menu_title">Streaming sites</string>

    <!--Películas-->
    <string name="film_title">Title</string>
    <string name="film_film">Films</string>

    <string name="movie_roma">Roma</string>
    <string name="movie_miresarriba">Dont Look Up</string>
    <string name="movie_novedadfrente">All Quiet on the Western Front</string>
    <string name="movie_poderperro">The Power of the Dog</string>
    <string name="movie_sociedadnieve">Society of the Snow</string>
    <string name="movie_irlandes">The Irishman</string>
    <string name="movie_pinocho">Pinocchio</string>
    <string name="movie_dune">Dune: Part Two</string>
    <string name="movie_manhana">Something from Tiffanys</string>
    <string name="movie_frozen">Frozen II</string>
    <string name="movie_espiritu">Spirited</string>

    <string name="sinopsis_titulo">Synopsis</string>

    <string name="sinopsis_roma">In early 1970s Mexico City, Cleo, a young domestic worker of Mixtec origin, works for a well-off middle-class family. The story unfolds in the Roma neighborhood, where the family’s seemingly peaceful life is shaken by marital tensions and social changes. Cleo not only faces her own personal challenges, including an unplanned pregnancy and a complicated relationship, but also becomes the emotional backbone of the family as it goes through a deep crisis. The film masterfully interweaves the personal with the political, depicting the 1971 student riots and the Corpus Christi Massacre as the backdrop to an intimate narrative about heartbreak, loneliness, and resilience. Every meticulously composed shot by Alfonso Cuarón reveals beauty in the everyday while exploring themes of class, gender, and memory in a transforming Mexico.</string>

    <string name="sinopsis_novedadfrente">An adaptation of Erich Maria Remarque’s classic novel, this film follows Paul Bäumer, an idealistic young German who, along with his school friends, enthusiastically enlists in the Imperial German Army during World War I. Motivated by patriotic speeches and the promise of glory, they soon discover the brutal reality of trench warfare on the Western Front. The film not only portrays the physical horrors of combat—the mud, the rats, the mustard gas, the bayonet charges—but also the psychological toll that turns these young men into disillusioned, traumatized adults. Through viscerally realistic scenes, the film explores how the war machine consumes the humanity of everyone involved, Germans and French alike, questioning nationalism, heroism, and the true cost of a conflict that left a lost generation behind.</string>

    <string name="sinopsis_miresarriba">University astronomer Kate Dibiasky and her professor, Dr. Randall Mindy, discover a planet-sized comet headed directly toward Earth, with an expected impact in six months that would trigger a mass extinction event. What begins as an exciting scientific discovery quickly becomes a bureaucratic and media nightmare as they try to warn the world. The film fiercely satirizes the contemporary response to crises, featuring a president more concerned with midterm elections, media outlets that trivialize the news, tech magnates with selfish solutions, and a population divided between denial and fanaticism. As the comet approaches, the film becomes an allegory for climate change, disinformation, and humanity’s inability to respond to existential threats even when the evidence is overwhelming.</string>

    <string name="sinopsis_poderperro">Set in rural Montana in 1925, the film follows brothers Phil and George Burbank, successful ranchers who are emotionally distant. Phil, intelligent, cruel, and charismatic, completely dominates his kinder but passive brother. When George secretly marries Rose, a lonely widow, and brings her teenage son, Peter, to the ranch, Phil begins a campaign of psychological intimidation against them. However, Peter—seemingly fragile but astute—starts carefully observing Phil, uncovering his vulnerabilities and secrets. What follows is a tense psychological game of power, repressed desire, and revenge, where appearances deceive and each character hides deep layers of complexity. The film explores toxic masculinity, the loneliness of the rural American heartland, and the subtle ways power can corrupt and be corrupted.</string>

    <string name="sinopsis_sociedadnieve">Based on the real 1972 Andes tragedy, the film recounts the story of Uruguayan Air Force Flight 571, which was carrying the Old Christians Club rugby team and some of their relatives to Chile. After crashing in the mountains at over 3,500 meters of altitude, the 29 initial survivors must face extreme conditions: subzero temperatures, lack of food, deadly avalanches, and the desperate wait for a rescue that never comes. As days turn into weeks, the group is forced to make impossible decisions to survive, including the cannibalism of the deceased. The film examines not only the physical struggle for survival but also the moral, psychological, and spiritual complexities they face, as well as the human bonds that are formed and broken under extreme pressure, all while clinging to hope against all odds.</string>

    <string name="sinopsis_irlandes">Through the eyes of Frank Sheeran, a World War II veteran turned truck driver and later hitman, the film chronicles decades of American criminal history. Sheeran, portrayed by a digitally aged Robert De Niro, enters the world of the mafia through Russell Bufalino and soon becomes the trusted man of powerful union leader Jimmy Hoffa. The more-than-three-and-a-half-hour epic follows the complex relationship between Sheeran and Hoffa—from their friendship to their eventual rupture—against the backdrop of union corruption, mafia family wars, and government interference. Martin Scorsese weaves a melancholic reflection on time, loyalty, betrayal, and regret, portraying not only the rise and fall of criminal empires but also the personal cost of a life of violence and the shadows that haunt a man in his final days.</string>

    <string name="sinopsis_pinocho">In fascist Italy of the 1930s, Geppetto, an elderly woodcarver devastated by the loss of his son Carlo during World War I, creates a wooden puppet in a drunken act of despair. Magically, the puppet is brought to life by a forest spirit—but not as the perfect child Geppetto hoped for. This version of Pinocchio, faithful to the dark tone of Collodi’s original tales, follows the puppet on a journey of self-discovery through a world full of dangers: from an exploitative circus run by the sinister Count Volpe to a paradisiacal island that turns children into donkeys to sell them. Guillermo del Toro uses this story to explore themes of blind obedience versus independent thought, the nature of real humanity versus artificial perfection, and unconditional paternal love, all set in an Italy grappling with its own identity crisis under fascist rule.</string>

    <string name="sinopsis_dune">In the distant future, the noble Paul Atreides, son of Duke Leto Atreides and the Bene Gesserit Lady Jessica, is brought to the desert planet Arrakis, also known as Dune. This arid world is the sole source of the spice melange, the most valuable substance in the universe, which enables interstellar navigation, prolongs life, and expands consciousness. When House Atreides is betrayed and destroyed by their rivals, the Harkonnens, with the Emperor’s complicity, Paul must flee into the desert, where he joins the Fremen, the native inhabitants of Arrakis. As Paul discovers his destiny as the Kwisatz Haderach (a kind of prophesied messiah), he must navigate precognitive visions, interstellar political wars, planetary ecology, and his own humanity as he leads a revolution that will change the universe forever.</string>

    <string name="sinopsis_frozen">Three years after the events of the first film, Elsa—now Queen of Arendelle—begins to hear a mysterious voice calling to her from afar. This voice leads her, along with her sister Anna, ice harvester Kristoff, reindeer Sven, and snowman Olaf, on a journey beyond their kingdom to the Enchanted Forest, a magical territory surrounded by impenetrable mist. There they discover the truth about Elsa’s powers and their family’s origins, meeting the Northuldra, a people who live in harmony with the magical spirits of nature. The film explores themes of identity, destiny, maturity, and the power of familial love as the characters face challenges that test their bonds and reveal long-buried secrets about the kingdom of Arendelle.</string>

    <string name="sinopsis_manhana">Rachel, a young New Yorker, discovers that her fiancé—an apparently perfect surgeon—has been cheating on her just before Christmas. Devastated and confused, she accidentally exchanges gift bags at Tiffany and Co. with Gary, a single father who is equally disillusioned with love. What begins as a casual encounter to return the gifts becomes a series of dates and shared moments that lead both to question their ideas about love and relationships. As they navigate family expectations during the holidays and confront their own fears of commitment, Rachel and Gary discover that sometimes love arrives when you least expect it and in the most unconventional packages.</string>

    <string name="sinopsis_espiritu">In this innovative musical take on Charles Dickens’ classic, Clint Briggs, the Ghost of Christmas Present, is tired of his annual job of redeeming souls. He decides to take on an impossible case: that of Eric Whittle, a cynical and ruthless media consultant whose mission is to sow division and controversy online. What Clint doesn’t anticipate is that Eric might be the first irredeemable subject in history. With help from the Ghosts of Christmas Past and Future, Clint embarks on a musical adventure filled with elaborate numbers, sharp humor, and heartfelt moments that explore not only the redemption of a man but also the importance of human connection, kindness, and the Christmas spirit in an increasingly digital and divided world.</string>

    <!--Ayuda-->
    <string name="help_screen_title">Help</string>
    <string name="help_screen">WELCOME TO FILMOTECA

Your personal app to explore the world of streaming. Filmoteca brings all the major platforms together in one place, allowing you to discover and organize your favorite entertainment in an intuitive and comprehensive way.

HOW TO USE THE APP:

On the main screen, you will see all available platforms: Netflix, HBO, Disney+, Amazon Prime, and Apple TV. Simply tap on the one you are interested in to access its full movie catalog.

Within each platform, movies are arranged in an easy-to-navigate grid. Each movie displays its poster and title. By tapping any movie, you will access a full detail screen with extensive information: detailed synopsis, director, release year, duration, genre, and rating.

To navigate, use the back arrow in the top left corner or your device’s swipe-back gesture. All screens allow smooth scrolling to read extended content.

AVAILABLE INFORMATION:

Each movie includes a complete synopsis describing the plot, characters, and context. You will also find accurate technical details: director, production year, exact duration, and film genre. Ratings help you identify critically acclaimed movies.

The app is regularly updated with new releases and featured content from each platform. You can freely explore all platforms without switching between apps.

PRACTICAL TIPS:

- Explore all platforms: each one has exclusive content worth discovering.
- Read full synopses by scrolling down on the detail screen.
- Use director and genre information to find similar movies.
- Check ratings as a reference for quality.
- Navigate freely between screens using the back buttons.

FUTURE FEATURES:

We are working on new features coming soon: favorites system to save movies, advanced search by multiple criteria, personalized recommendations based on your interests, filters by genre and year, offline mode to access information without internet, notifications for new releases, calendar integration for release reminders, option to share movies with friends, reviews and comments section, and integrated trailers.

We also plan technical improvements such as performance optimization, reduced data usage, support for more languages, enhanced accessibility for all users, and compatibility with more devices and screen sizes.

FREQUENTLY ASKED QUESTIONS:

Do I need a subscription to use Filmoteca? No, the app is completely free and only displays information about available content.

Can I watch movies directly from the app? Filmoteca is an informational catalog. To watch content, you need a subscription to the respective platforms.

How often is it updated? The catalog is regularly updated with new releases and featured movies.

Can I suggest movies? Yes, we welcome suggestions to improve and expand the catalog.

Does it use a lot of data? It only downloads optimized images and text, so consumption is minimal.

PRIVACY AND SECURITY:

Filmoteca respects your privacy. We do not collect personal data, do not require registration or login, do not share information with third parties, do not display invasive ads, and comply with all current data protection regulations.

CONTACT AND SUPPORT:

If you need help, first check this section. Make sure you have the latest app version installed and verify your internet connection. If you encounter persistent issues, restart the app. For additional technical assistance, contact our support team.

OUR MISSION:

We believe entertainment should be accessible, organized, and enjoyable for everyone. Our goal is to help you discover amazing content without information overload, providing a clean, intuitive, and comprehensive experience that complements your streaming journey.

Thank you for choosing Filmoteca. Happy cinematic exploration!

Last update: December 2024
Version: 1.0.0</string>


</resources>